in short i'm glenn renfro you're going
简而言之，我是格伦·伦弗罗，你要去
to say who is this guy I am a right now
说我现在是谁
I'm a committer on XD I've been doing
我是我一直在做的XD的提交者
everything from working with you know
与您合作的一切都知道
production-ready systems for companies
公司的生产就绪系统
I've done consulting a lot of it's been
我已经做了很多咨询
I've did a stint with a editor of ours
我曾在我们的编辑任职
bidon whoa limiting competitor of ours
bidon谁是我们的极限竞争对手
with caching and so I had a lot of
缓存，所以我有很多
experience dealing with heavy volumes of
有大量的处理经验
data coming in and being able to handle
数据进入并能够处理
that data and a lot of times I get a
这些数据，很多时候我得到了
spring integration to do that and the
春天整合做到这一点，
reason why I was spring integration was
我之所以进行 Spring Integration 的原因是
just so easy to test so in this
就是这么容易测试
discussion today what brought about this
今天的讨论导致了什么
you know spring integration done
你知道弹簧整合完成了
beautifully is back in December when we
精美的是回到十二月
were doing working on XD XD had been
在做XD的工作XD已经
previously named another project and
以前命名另一个项目，并且
then formally got it kicked off as
然后正式开始
spring XD it was a traditional spring
XD春天，这是一个传统的春天
application okay every sense of the word
应用程序可以理解所有单词
and one of the things that we saw was
我们看到的一件事是
Dave sire had certainly been introducing
戴夫（Dave）父亲肯定是在介绍
it and spring boot was became kind of
它和 spring boot 变得有点
the ideas like okay the future of any
这样的想法好吗？
kind of new application is going to be
一种新的应用程序将是
spring boot and I think next year when
spring boot ，我想明年
you come if you have a chance to come to
如果有机会你就来
spring one what you're going to see is a
春天，你会看到的是
lot more people not saying something
很多人不说话
done with boot or done bootiful you're
完成引导或完成引导后，
just going to see the demos and their
只是去看演示和他们的
presentations going to be doing nothing
演示将无所作为
but spring boot not going to sip and I'm
但是 spring boot 不会to饮而我
starting to kind of see that in the
开始有点在
environment as well as people are saying
环境以及人们所说的
hey you know when I'm starting a new
嘿，你知道我什么时候开始新的
project or even kind of messing around
项目甚至是一团糟
instead of you know working with you
而不是你知道和你一起工作
know starting from scratch and when you
知道从头开始，当你
use boot so you're going to see a lot of
使用启动，所以您将看到很多
that and we actually did do that it's
那，而我们确实做到了
kind of old-fashioned saying eat your
有点老套话
own dog food we went ahead and
自己吃狗粮，我们继续前进，
retrofitted something had been worked on
改装了一些东西
for a bit almost a year and made it into
花了将近一年的时间
spring boot and you saw how did that
spring boot ，你看到了
turn out well in short
总之好
we had one sprint two weeks print which
我们有一个冲刺，两个星期的打印
we had one day Lovett developer kind of
我们有一天Lovett开发人员
dedicated to that task and he took XD
致力于这项工作，他接受了XD
and moved it to spring boot and we're
并将其移至 spring boot ，我们
not talking a small apps XD is big but
不谈论小型应用程序XD很大，但
then we had about another sprint where
然后我们还有另一个冲刺
we kind of tweaked a little bit and the
我们有点调整了
rest of us how to kind of get used to
我们其余的人如何习惯
and I think it get used to we had
我认为它已经习惯了
already set up some kind of conventions
已经建立了某种约定
on her own and spring XD and when we
她自己和春天的XD，以及当我们
went to boot it was a you know there was
去启动它是一个你知道那里
that little bit of a learning curve not
那一点学习曲线不是
a lot but we were used to doing it X but
很多，但是我们习惯了X
now we had to do it why it wasn't a huge
现在我们必须这样做，为什么它不是很大
gap it was just a small gap so another
差距只是一个很小的差距，所以另一个
part of another sprint was us kind of
另一个冲刺的一部分是我们
getting to the cadence of it and that's
踏上节奏，那就是
anytime you do anything new so it so the
每当您做任何新的事情时，
goal is is if you have a key exists and
目标是您是否有钥匙存在并且
you're working on it can you go from
你正在努力，你可以从
spring straight spring to strain it to
弹力直弹簧
spring boot the answer is yes what you
spring boot 答案是肯定的你
will gain is as you've seen all these
将会收获如您所见
things all the other presentations you
所有其他演示文稿
gain speed and you're coding you know
加快速度，您正在编码，就知道
it's up to you if you want to invest
如果您要投资，则取决于您
that time in it but i would highly
那个时候，但我会高度
recommend certainly do maybe I look at
推荐当然做，也许我看看
it as a possibility as you already heard
正如您已经听到的那样
Gradle is going down that path as well
Gradle也沿着这条路走
so if you know your apps going to be out
因此，如果您知道自己的应用即将发布
there for ten plus years and by the way
在那里呆了十多年
can I just show a hands how many of you
我可以举手吗？
guys have an app that's older than five
伙计们的应用早于五个
years old oh so you look at this maybe
岁哦，所以你看这个也许
that's something if you're doing
如果你在做的话
something new or maybe something that's
一些新的东西或者也许是
all a couple years old made us something
几岁就让我们有所作为
you need to look into okay so that was
您需要研究一下，以便
kind of impetus to this so what I want
这种动力，所以我想要
to kind of bring out in our conversation
在我们的对话中展现出来
today also I'm going to be kind of
今天我也要
sensitive on time y'all have done
准时的敏感你们都做了
fantastic Taylor this is probably one of
梦幻般的泰勒，这可能是其中之一
the better spring ones I've been to and
我去过的更好的春天
I just I mean give yourself a hand y'all
我只是想给自己一个机会
did great so
做得很好
I'm proud of you guys all right they
我为你们没事感到骄傲
getting back into it we're going to be
回到它，我们将成为
doing a couple things by the time you
到时候你做几件事
leave this program if you have never
如果您从来没有离开过这个程序
done spring integration before I want
在我想要之前完成了 Spring Integration
you to be able to take and go to my
你能够带走去我的
github site pull it down and you should
github站点把它拉下来，你应该
be able to at least understand the basic
至少能够理解基本
of a spring integration application
弹簧集成应用程序
whether you're already doing it in a
是否已经在
spring base way you should be able to do
你应该能够做的春季基地
that by or you're doing a spring app you
那个或者你正在做一个春季应用
should be able to put in spring
应该可以放在春天
integration in without always having to
整合而不必总是
put boot but also we're going to show
放靴子，但我们还要展示
you how to build an application from
您如何从中构建应用程序
scratch using spring boot in spring
在春季使用 spring boot 刮擦
integration the other thing that we're
整合我们要做的另一件事
going to be covering is yes sir huh at
会掩盖的是的，先生，在
the end of the presentation I have a
演示的结尾我有一个
links to it and I will pop those up and
链接到它，我将弹出它们，
if I and if you don't like the
如果我和你不喜欢
presentation that's why or if you do
这就是为什么或如果您这样做的演示文稿
like it that's my Twitter right there so
就像那就是我的Twitter，所以
we're going to be kind of going through
我们将经历
that part of it so there's two things
这部分，所以有两件事
we're going to be other going to be
我们将成为另一个
covering today is one of the things i am
涵盖今天是我的事情之一
i'm an uber device geek let's put it
我是一个超级设备怪胎
that way and I ever since college and
这样，我从大学开始
after college I worked with devices and
大学毕业后，我使用设备
how device to plug and devices capture
设备如何插入和设备捕获
their data use their data for whatever
他们的数据将他们的数据用于任何用途
purpose and so I'll needed to talk about
目的，所以我需要谈论
that I have been drinking so much coffee
我喝了那么多咖啡
you're going to hear me go fast if you
你会听到我走的快
need me to slow down certainly let me
需要我放慢速度，当然让我
know because after today I'm going to
知道，因为在今天之后，我要去
have the world's worst headache because
头疼得厉害，因为
when people keep giving me free coffee I
当人们不断给我免费咖啡时
never say no so let's go and get started
永远不要拒绝，让我们开始吧
so kind of going back into that kind of
所以回到那种
geekiness and loving the ability to go
讨厌和热爱去的能力
in and actually work with application or
并实际与应用程序一起工作或
work with devices capturing that data
与捕获该数据的设备一起使用
but back then it was always plugs right
但是那时候它一直都是正确的
you plug it in device to capture device
您将其插入设备以捕获设备
but now what we're looking at is the
但是现在我们正在寻找的是
Internet of Things the ability to have
物联网具备的能力
devices that are remote
远程设备
communicating back to a server gathering
通讯回服务器集合
their data right and it's a machine to
他们的数据权利，这是一台机器
machine of beginning of where the
起点的机器
internet used to always kind of be the
互联网过去一直是
endpoint was people now we're seeing the
终点是人们，现在我们看到了
endpoints or machines or people so in
端点，机器或人
this case that's where MQTT came in MQTT
这种情况是MQTT出现在MQTT中的地方
stands for and you know what I'm going
代表，你知道我要去
to go ahead and read it off my script
继续阅读我的脚本
here message queue to Liberty transport
这里消息队列到自由传输
it's about five to ten years old I think
我认为大约五到十岁
it's about 10 years old and it came from
它大约有10年的历史了，它来自
the sense that what you have is if you
如果你拥有的话
have the device where bandwidth or
将设备放在带宽或
battery life is critical you want to
电池续航时间至关重要
keep your messages short and concise so
使您的信息简短明了
that's what this does this is allow you
这就是这样做的目的是让你
to admit small messages from these
接受来自这些的小消息
devices and be able to save that battery
设备并能够节省电池
or bandwidth of like one railroad
或一条铁路的带宽
actually uses still a 9600 baud way to
实际上仍然使用9600波特率
do track switching okay messages need to
跟踪切换好消息需要
be small yes you got that yeah still out
很小，是的，你知道，还是
there I don't know if it was Kermit or
那里我不知道是不是Kermit还是
not that's it for you guys are older
不是，因为你们年纪大了
than me or actually if I said it on that
比我好，或者如果我说过
old but we're getting things from oil
旧了，但我们从石油中得到东西
rigs vehicles retail stores sensor data
钻机车辆零售商店传感器数据
another example that's out there is
另一个例子是
refrigerator so we have a soda
冰箱，所以我们有苏打水
manufacturer out there that actually has
那里实际上有制造商
device has a their compressor emits
设备有其压缩机发出的声音
messages back to the home office based
邮件返回到家庭办公室
on that compressor utilization they can
在压缩机的利用率上，他们可以
actually go in and no okay based on how
实际进去，基于
this compressor is behaving the machine
这台压缩机运转机器
is empty we need to send somebody out
是空的，我们需要派人出去
there to go ahead and monitor or go
在那里继续监视或去
ahead nut mantra but go ahead and refill
提前螺母咒语，但继续并补充
that machine so just in time product
那台机器，所以及时的产品
fulfillment into a refrigerator second
履行第二冰箱
thing is is if the compressor is having
问题是，如果压缩机有
errors they notice in a prepare person
他们在准备人员中发现的错误
or a person swap out the refrigerator
或一个人换掉冰箱
thirdly it has a GPS in it so if the
第三，它有一个GPS，所以如果
Messiah refrigerator starts moving
弥赛亚冰箱开始移动
site they know it's stolen they can call
他们知道可以打电话的网站被盗
the police so it's kind of an overall
警察，所以总体来说
view of the world we also have where
世界观，我们也有哪里
medical devices are actually beginning
医疗设备实际上正在开始
to emit messages where you can actually
发出消息，您实际上可以
go in and know where the device is in
走进去，知道设备在哪里
good condition or not and to a point I'm
状况良好与否，某种程度上我
not sure they've gotten this far along
不确定他们已经走了这么远
but I did hear some whispers where we
但我确实听到了一些耳语
actually have some vendors out there
实际上有一些供应商
that you have a patient in the in the
你有一个病人在
hospital room and the device is emitting
病房并且设备正在发射
messages saying okay this person is you
消息说这个人是你
know here's his vital stats and whatnot
知道这是他的重要数据
and I've had exposure to medical devices
而且我接触过医疗设备
in the past one quick aside just out of
在过去的一旁
college my first project it was very
大学我的第一个项目是
proud of his I wrote software that would
为他感到骄傲，我编写了
track a patient from the time they left
从他们离开的时间开始追踪患者
entered it o our to the time they left
在他们离开时输入我们的时间
an alarm this particular device is
该特定设备的警报
called a Merlin and it was at the time
叫梅林，那时
state-of-the-art it allows you to
最新的技术，它使您能够
capture spo2 which is your blood oxygen
捕获血液中的spo2
temperature EKG ECG and so you had a
温度心电图心电图，所以你有一个
full stat of what was happening to a
发生了什么的完整统计
patient when they're in the bar now this
现在他们在酒吧的时候耐心点
has actually been brought outside the
实际上已经带到外面了
o.r to other areas but in this
或其他地区，但在此
particular case the way that the Merlin
特殊情况下，Merlin的方式
made its money is not just by the base
赚钱不只是靠基地
unit being kind of pricey but it was the
单位有点贵，但这是
adapters you got each of those sensors
每个传感器都有一个适配器
was an adapter and so what we could do
是一个适配器，所以我们能做些什么
when we were testing it was we always
当我们测试时，我们总是
put it in diagnostic mode the world's
将其置于全球诊断模式
perfect patient you know his heart rate
完美的病人，你知道他的心律
was always right his pulse was always
永远是对的，他的脉搏永远是
right and we kept going back to our
对，我们一直回到我们的
managers saying that's great but we need
经理说那很棒，但我们需要
erroneous data what happens we want to
错误的数据我们想要发生什么
do a plug out test alright pull the plug
做一个插头测试好了拔插头
what happens if what if the you know
如果你知道怎么办
patients getting erratic data the sensor
患者获取不稳定数据的传感器
is wrong we won't be able to capture
是错误的，我们将无法捕获
that data and know how it behaves and
该数据并了解其行为方式，
management was rather resistant so
管理相当抗拒，所以
finally one day they told us and I can't
终于有一天他们告诉我们，我不能
remember the exact part number but it
记住确切的零件号，但是
was like s 320 for a part has been
就像320年代的一部分
ordered it's on its way and we went
命令它在路上，我们去了
great haha get to real have sense we're
伟大的哈哈变得真实有道理，我们
going to put the little spo2 sensor on
将把小的spo2传感器放在
our finger will be able to track it well
我们的手指就能很好地追踪
we got the part in and we found out our
我们参与其中，我们发现了我们的
management had a very very bad sense of
管理层的感觉非常非常糟糕
humor it was a temperature sensor and
幽默，这是一个温度传感器，
it's not the one that you would put in
这不是您要放入的那个
your child's ear it's not like the glass
你孩子的耳朵不像玻璃杯
one we used to use when we grew up and
我们长大后曾经使用过的
went somewhere completely different and
去了一个完全不同的地方
we all at the same time I'm not kidding
我们都在同一时间我不是在开玩笑
our group went oh so needless to save to
我们小组去了哦，所以不必保存
capture sensor readings we held it in
捕获我们保存在其中的传感器读数
our hand so so what we're not going to
我们的手，所以我们不会
the device I wanted to use this week has
我本周要使用的设备有
not arrived so we're going to simulate
还没到，所以我们要模拟
another device so we're going to
另一个设备，所以我们要
actually have real extra will be writing
实际上有真正的额外会写
to eps in our demo today the first app
今天在我们的演示中第一个应用程序
is going to be a traditional spring
将是一个传统的春天
application this traditional spring
应用这个传统的春天
application is going to actually go out
应用程序将实际退出
and to go to a couple of trading floors
并去几个交易大厅
and gather bitcoin US dollar to bitcoin
并收集比特币美元到比特币
conversion rate and it's going to take
转换率，这将需要
that data it's going to translate that
该数据将转换为
data into a common format that data is
数据转换为通用格式
going to be then emitted the MQTT out to
然后将MQTT发出给
a rabbit broker once that bat rabbit
一只兔子经纪人，那只蝙蝠兔子
boker actually gets that data it's going
博克实际上获取了要发送的数据
to post it to a topic we're going to
将其发布到我们将要讨论的主题
have a spring boot app that we're going
有一个我们要去的Spring Boot应用程序
to write that's going to actually go in
写，这将实际上进入
grab that data off and display it to
抓取数据并将其显示给
console it's also going to be a very
控制台，这也将是一个非常
weak I say week basic in spring it bc
弱，我说每周基本在春季
app that's going to be a part of the
该应用程序将成为
boot that's going to allow you to go to
引导，这将允许您转到
a browser and view the current message
浏览器并查看当前消息
count and then we're going to talk a
数，然后我们要谈一个
little bit about the actuator and we're
关于执行器的一点点，我们
going to be able to measure the health
能够测量健康
of our spring boot app and the goal is
我们的 spring boot 应用程序，目标是
again is that convention over
再次是约定
configuration this stuff comes right out
配置这个东西马上出来
of the box you don't have to do anything
不需要你做任何事情
and that's some of the things we learned
这就是我们学到的一些东西
in Spring XD it was like we were so used
在Spring XD中，就像我们被习惯了一样
to having to go in and configure beans
必须进入并配置bean
and yeah set these beans up which was
是的，设置这些豆子是
always great but now it's already set up
总是很棒，但现在已经设置好了
for you all you have to do is in
对你来说，你要做的就是
food just to look like a little starter
食物只是看起来像一个入门
palm and we're going to talk a little
棕榈，我们要谈一点
bit about that one final note Bitcoin
关于最后一点说明比特币
this is not a mining operation so if you
这不是采矿作业，所以如果您
think we're going to be making a lot of
认为我们将做出很多
money we're not so one other thing we're
钱，我们不是，我们是另一件事
going to do and it's a little aside this
要做的事，这一点
is a little bit of pride moment i'm
我有点骄傲
going to show you how we can actually
向您展示我们如何才能真正
even take that spring boot app and not
甚至不带那个 spring boot 应用
even use spring boot but you spring XD
甚至使用 spring boot ，但您弹簧XD
and in one line of code be able to
并在一行代码中能够
capture that data and log that data out
捕获数据并将其注销
with just one line of a stream so that's
只需一行流，所以
that's a little bit of pride there i
那是我的骄傲
just wanted to show XD because i work on
只是想展示XD，因为我从事
it spring boo you've probably seen this
春天嘘你可能已经看到了这个
slide about a hundred times last year
去年滑了一百次
this year what we're going to be
今年我们将成为
covering is again it takes a pin unit of
覆盖是再次需要一个针单位
you it's a convention over configuration
你是配置的约定
the parts we're going to really cover
我们将要涵盖的部分
today is the just we're going to create
今天是我们要创造的
a base app so it's going to be a bit
一个基本的应用程序，所以会有点
we're going to use an embedded tomcat
我们将使用嵌入式tomcat
that comes with it we're going to show
我们将展示它附带的
you how to set that up which there's not
您如何设置没有
that much we're going to talk about the
那就是我们要谈论的
opinionated starter palms i'm going to
自以为是的初学者手掌
show you a little bit of an aside to
展示给你一点
something that they didn't cover and
他们没有涵盖的东西
that is what if your opinion is
那就是如果你的意见是
different than the opinion of the
与众不同
starter palm what do you do we're also
初学者手掌您还做什么？
going to yeah and the other thing that
是的，另一件事是
i'm going to be doing is how many of you
我要做的就是你们有多少人
guys I'll put this way I went to I was
伙计们，我会这样说，我去了
in that league like Atlanta spring user
像亚特兰大春季用户那样的联盟
group I'm one of the guys that certainly
我当然是其中的一员
helped man that up so when you went to
帮助了那个，所以当你去
like a sugg I asked a guy said how many
像一个建议，我问一个人说多少
of you are going to be using purely
你们中的人将纯粹使用
annotations from now on and I want to
从现在开始，我想
ask you how many if you're if you were
问你如果你是多少
to start a new app would use XML or
要启动新应用，将使用XML或
annotations can I have a show hands of
注释可以显示出来吗
those people who would just go straight
那些会直走的人
annotation all the way okay how many of
一直注释，有多少个
you would actually still use XML look at
您实际上仍然会使用XML查看
that so what we're going to do is a part
所以我们要做的是一部分
of the spring boot app is it's going to
spring boot 应用程序的
have a bit of the annotations but it's
有一些注释，但是
also going to have we're going to show
也将有我们要展示
you how spring boot is not afraid to use
你怎么 spring boot 不怕用
XML
XML格式
so you guys who are used to xml you're
所以那些习惯使用xml的人
still supported okay so we're going to
仍然支持，所以我们要
show a little bit of that okay spring
展现春天的美好时光
integration so if you haven't had a
整合，如果您还没有
chance to play with it it is a basically
玩的机会，这基本上是
the spring implementation of the
春季实施
enterprise integration patterns okay if
企业整合模式还可以吗
you've ever seen the book it's about
您曾经看过这本关于
that thick I've seen it on many shelves
这么厚，我在很多架子上都看过
and most of the time it gathers dust or
而且大多数时候它会积聚灰尘或
holds up the other books because most of
持有其他书籍，因为大多数
time you go on the web and you find the
当您上网时，您会发现
patterns there and it's actually more
模式在那里，实际上更多
colorful whatever but the book how you
色彩缤纷，但书如何
still recommend having it it's that mean
仍然建议拥有它的意思是
it's very comprehensive and actually
它非常全面，实际上
does give you a lot more cases but
确实为您提供了更多案例，但是
spring is basically an implementation of
春天基本上是一个实现
that what again what I love about spring
那又是我对春天的爱
was is I had the ability and I'm going
是我有能力，我要去
to say this nasty word but in XML I can
说这个讨厌的词，但在XML中，我可以
make it testing a lot easier or through
使它的测试容易得多或通过
write Java config have it where I could
写Java配置有我可以的地方
actually go in through and be able to
实际经历并能够
say okay instead of I want to test a
说好吧，而不是我想测试一个
given stream or given flow right and
给定流或给定流权，以及
when I want to test it i don't want to
当我想要测试时，我不想
always have it right out to MQTT and
始终将其交给MQTT，
maybe I want to write that the result
也许我要写那个结果
transform results to follow something I
转换结果以跟随我
can test and that was repeatedly
可以测试，那是反复的
testable so that's what spring
可测试的，这就是春天
integration really helpful with is it
整合真的很有帮助吗
helps with that testing there was
帮助进行了测试
actually a discussion on that thing by
实际上是关于那个东西的讨论
marius on that topic and so i highly
marius在那个话题上，所以我非常
recommend watching that video on
建议您观看该视频
testability of spring or spring
弹簧或弹簧的可测试性
integration c-dawg my daughter just got
整合c-dawg我女儿刚得到
a dollar look at that she's getting rich
一美元的样子，她正在致富
but also with spring integration you
而且还可以通过Spring集成
have these adapters that allow you to
有这些适配器，使您能够
not only that allow internal flow of
不仅允许内部流动
data in your application but also
您的应用程序中的数据
externally we have it we have like rest
在外部，我们有它，我们喜欢休息
https ftp ftp rabbinic you JMS MQTT tcp
https ftp ftp阿拉伯语JMS MQTT tcp
and a whole list of adapters that if you
以及适配器的完整列表，如果您
have to communicate with other services
必须与其他服务进行通信
out there you're certainly allowed to do
在那里，您当然可以做
so so again i'm going to be a little bit
所以我再说一点
repetitive here the first thing we're
在这里重复第一件事
going to do is we're going to go ahead
我们要做的是继续前进
and create ASI application it's going to
并创建ASI应用
be a traditional application and you'll
成为传统应用程序，您将
see no real difference the second ones
看到第二个没有真正的区别
where you going to start seeing the
您将开始看到的
difference of the spring boot
spring boot 的区别
the data flow is going to be as follows
数据流将如下
we're going to see where we have
我们要看看我们在哪里
coinbase that's the online banking so
就是网上银行的coinbase
you can actually purchase bitcoins stand
您可以实际购买比特币摊位
have coinbase managed us for you so coin
让coinbase为您管理了我们，所以硬币
base is we're going to be gathering data
基础是我们将要收集数据
from it as far as their current bid
直到目前的出价
price against the coin and that's going
价格与硬币相对应
to be xml okay we're going to do a bit
成为xml好吧，我们将做一点
stamp and a bit stamp is going to be
邮票和一点邮票将是
annotation based so the one thing also
基于注释，所以一件事也
went to the guys who love XML or who
去了那些热爱XML或
love annotation if you already do an XML
喜欢注解（如果您已经做过XML）
and some lot of cases with people like
还有很多人喜欢的情况
the XML because they like that
XML，因为他们喜欢
flexibility of going in and changing
进入和变更的灵活性
sometimes annotations do work really
有时注释确实有效
well to say hey this is not going to
好说嘿，这不会
change or it's less likely change so
改变或改变的可能性较小，因此
annotations maybe something so you're
注释也许有些东西，所以你
allowed to mix and match and you'll see
允许混合搭配，您会看到
that certainly in this demo but they'll
当然在这个演示中，但他们会
both emit information once they receive
都在收到后发出信息
it and it's just going to be in their
它，它将只是在他们
JSON format we're going to translate
我们要翻译的JSON格式
that to a common JSON format and then
转换为通用JSON格式，然后
initially will write it to file but then
最初会将其写入文件，但随后
we're going to actually change this
我们将实际改变这一点
again at one magic Channel and I'm going
再次在一个魔术频道，我要去
to have it where it writes it out to
把它写在哪里
MQTT the MQTT monitor again is nothing
MQTT MQTT监视器再也不是什么了
more than just a basic of nothing more
不只是一个基本的
it's a spring boot app and it's uber
这是一个 spring boot 应用程序，它是超级
tiny and we're going to actually not
小，我们实际上不会
only write the or have the app there up
仅编写或在其中安装应用
and available but it's also going to be
和可用，但它也将是
something I'm going to show you how you
我要告诉你的事情
can actually go in and use the free of
可以真正进入并免费使用
charge jmx to monitor the condition of
向jmx充电以监视
your application write code to say what
您的应用程序写代码说什么
you know just because the app is up and
你知道因为应用程序启动了
it's running how do you know it's really
它正在运行，你怎么知道它真的
set and what's real status of my
设置以及我的真实状态是什么
application so I'm going to show you how
应用程序，所以我将向您展示
to write a health indicator and how the
编写健康指标以及如何
health indicator will you tell me what
健康指标你能告诉我什么
is up and what's down and that can be
上升了，下降了什么，那可能是
checked through a jmx so we're going to
通过一个jmx检查，所以我们要
actually kind of show you how to do that
实际上是向您展示如何做到这一点
as well what are our tools now I'm going
以及我现在要使用什么工具
to be using IntelliJ but this is there's
要使用IntelliJ，但这就是
two religious questions up here that
这里有两个宗教问题
usually cause fights among as the one
通常会引起一场战斗
was certainly XML or annotation based
肯定是基于XML或注释的
well it's your favorite editor i will be
好吧，这是你最喜欢的编辑器
using
使用
j we're going to be doing our bills
j我们要付账单
using Gradle w so when you pull down my
使用Gradle w，所以当您拉下我的
app from get you should be able to just
从得到的应用程序，您应该能够
run Gradle w run and if you even if you
运行Gradle w run，即使您
don't have Gradle installed it will pull
没有安装Gradle，它将拉动
down the necessary components and run
放下必要的组件并运行
the app of course yet nice a is optional
当然不错的应用程序是可选的
it's not you know but you have to
不是你知道，但你必须
certainly have get to pull the stuff
当然有拉东西
down but you can actually download the
下来，但您实际上可以下载
go to the site and download the app if
转到网站并下载应用程序，如果
you need it rabbit and Q is what we're
你需要它兔子，而Q就是我们
going to be using is our broker there's
将要使用的是我们的经纪人
only go quick aside here in RabbitMQ
在RabbitMQ中只在这里快点走
comes with the MQTT adapter already but
附带了MQTT适配器，但是
it's not enabled so you'll see there's
它没有启用，所以您会看到
this little tiny line up underneath it
它下面的小细线
that shows you how to say rabbit MN
那告诉你怎么说兔子MN
plugins enable rabbit any cute rabbit
插件可以让任何可爱的兔子兔
mmm cute underscore MQTT so once you
mmm可爱的下划线MQTT，所以一旦您
even have it enabled you're ready to
甚至启用它，您就可以准备
rock as far as rabbits concern a library
就兔子而言，岩石就是图书馆
is get or spring boot spring integration
是get或spring boot spring集成
I did put a little bit of Jackson in
我确实放了一点杰克逊
here because I'm going to be handling
在这里，因为我要处理
the transform but spring integration
转型但春天整合
already has a bunch of transforms in it
已经有很多转换了
already I just wanted to write some more
我已经想写更多了
code sorry I miss coat all the
对不起，我想念所有外套
annotations man alright so what does our
注释人很好，那么我们做什么
regular Oh spring application look like
普通哦春季申请看起来像
again we're going to be doing XML setup
再次，我们将要进行XML设置
of our coinbase HTTP outbound gateway
我们的coinbase HTTP出站网关
we're going to be setting up our main
我们将要建立我们的主要
the advertising for dot 0 there whew
点0的广告在那里
we're going to show you a little bit the
我们将向您展示一些
new for of stuff that's coming out for
即将推出的新东西
has already come out for spring
春天已经出来了
integration okay there was a
整合好了
conversation or a discussion that came
谈话或讨论
out on Tuesday morning by gary russell
加里·罗素（Gary russell）在星期二早上出去
he did a phenomenal job especially
他做得特别出色
probably because him and artem wrote it
可能是因为他和阿尔泰姆写了它
for spring for integration for one and
春季为一体
for the highly recommend g because he
强烈推荐g，因为他
does go through a heist overview a
确实经过了抢劫概述
high-level overview of all the new stuff
所有新内容的高级概述
that's come out with it but we will be
出来了，但我们会
touching on some of that here
在这里谈一些
we're going to be setting up our
我们将要建立我们的
transform we're going to be setting up a
转变，我们将要建立一个
bit stamp outbound gateway the
位标记出站网关
annotation and then lastly the IMP we're
注释，最后是我们的IMP
going to go a little bit of a deep dive
会深入一点
because Gary had made a request he said
因为加里提出了要求，他说
he's getting a lot of questions about
他有很多关于的问题
the MQTT adapter and MQTT he said can
他说可以的MQTT适配器和MQTT
you spend just a little bit of time
你只花一点时间
discussing you know some of the features
讨论您知道一些功能
of MQTT and I said absolutely so we're
我说的绝对是，所以我们
going to spend about a couple three four
要花大约三四两
minutes going down that path so let's go
分钟走那条路，让我们走
and get started so the first thing I'm
然后开始，所以我的第一件事
going to go ahead and do is we're going
要继续前进，要做的就是我们要前进
to go ahead and do a components can so
继续做一个组件可以做到
we can find all the components that's
我们可以找到所有的
involved an amazing thing about spring
与春天有关
is is it's got to the point where with
是到了要点
spring boot it practically writes itself
实际上它自己写的spring boot
but the original spring kind of did that
但是最初的春天是那样的
already so I'm gonna let it write the
已经，所以我要让它写
code for me I also found out that when I
我的代码我也发现，当我
allow if I record the ability for it to
如果我记录它的能力，请允许
write the if I coded it I did this like
写如果我编码，我这样做
two days ago ice Mike talks sped up
两天前，冰麦克的会谈加快了
because usually i found out when i was
因为通常我会发现我何时
sitting there typing i quit talking so
坐在那里打字我不说话了
i'm going to let my past do it for me so
我要让过去为我做
we're gonna do a component scan the
我们将对组件进行扫描
thing that's in 40 is called enable
40岁的人称为启用
integration and the past if you did
整合和过去（如果您这样做的话）
spring integration you had to have xml
春天的整合，你必须有XML
okay but now with the 40 you don't have
好的，但是现在有了40个您就没有了
to but you do have to have the enable
到，但您必须启用
integration there so it basically
整合在那里，所以基本上
bootstraps your spring integration we
引导您的 Spring Integration ，我们
are going to be again using an xml by
将会再次使用xml
the way that's not necessary here since
因为这里没有必要的方式
we do or using the xml but i felt that
我们这样做或使用xml，但我觉得
was something kind of important to you
对你来说很重要
know say make sure if you're doing
知道说确定你是否在做
strictly annotation base make sure you
严格注释基础确保您
have that the import resource again
再次拥有导入资源
integration xml and again nothing new
集成xml，再也没有新内容
here it's a hello world but what we're
这是一个世界你好，但我们
doing is we added the annotation config
要做的是我们添加了注释配置
application context so now that we have
应用程序上下文，现在我们有了
that setup let's go ahead and set up our
该设置让我们继续进行设置
transform our transform is going to be
转变我们的转变将是
nothing more than a component
只不过是一个组件
and we're going to go ahead and make
我们将继续前进
this into a transform and notice it's
变成一个转换，注意它是
annotated again there's times where
再次注释有时
maybe annotations not evil XML guys and
也许注释不是邪恶的XML专家，
GE annotation guys maybe XML is not all
GE注释专家也许不是XML
that evil if I've been asked they said
如果有人问我，那是邪恶的
what r yes i'm eighty-percent annotation
什么是我百分之八十的注解
twenty percent XML when I XML kicks in
当我使用XML时，百分之二十的XML
that's usually when I'm like we're gonna
通常是当我想我们要
have to do testing us on XML side of me
必须在我的XML方面对我们进行测试
secure comes out so in this case what it
安全出来，所以在这种情况下
is it's going to have an input channel
是否会有输入通道
the transform channel it's going to
转换通道
output that to file so let's take a
输出到文件，所以让我们
second and look at my xml and by the way
第二，顺便看看我的xml
i do i've been coding on the Eclipse and
我确实在Eclipse上进行编码，
IntelliJ no preference they like them
IntelliJ没有喜欢他们的偏好
both so the transform channel we talked
两者都如此，我们谈到的转换渠道
about let's go ahead and go back up here
关于我们继续前进，回到这里
so we are so how we gathering our data
所以我们就是这样，我们如何收集我们的数据
from our coinbase HTTP is we were
来自我们的coinbase HTTP，
basically using an inbound channel
基本上使用入站通道
adapter here that's going to be a polar
这里的适配器将是极性的
it's going to be going in and polling
这将要进行轮询
and basically once every ten seconds
基本上每十秒钟一次
right it's going to emit an empty
对，它会发出一个空的
message it's not really doing anything
消息，它实际上并没有做任何事情
here it's just gathering information but
这里只是收集信息，但是
if I wanted to I could to put an
如果我想我可以放一个
expression a spell expression in here
在这里表达一个咒语表达
that maybe does something and maybe put
那也许做点什么，也许把
some data and put in the message in this
一些数据，并在此放入消息中
case I just need to fact that hey every
情况下，我只需要事实证明
10 seconds let me know something's going
10秒让我知道发生了什么
on that message this coinbase HTTP is
在该消息上，这个coinbase HTTP是
going to go down to here right I'm going
要走到这里，我要走了
to try to see maybe I could squeeze this
尝试看看也许我可以挤压这个
down a little bit sorry not much as
有点遗憾
small as it gets ya had a you can ask
小，因为它有你可以问
the camera guy I was having so much fun
我很开心的相机人
with the settings on this monitor Ike
在此显示器上的设置
actually came out twice trying to get it
实际上出来两次试图得到它
right and I my machine is just evil so
是的，我的机器是邪恶的，所以
but in this case that message is going
但是在这种情况下
to be delivered to our coinbase gateway
交付给我们的coinbase网关
right and the coin based gateway is
对，基于硬币的网关是
going to make a request out to the coin
向硬币发出请求
based site it's going to do a get sorry
基于网站，这会变得很抱歉
about all the things popping up there
关于那里突然出现的所有事情
and it's going to send it to the
并将其发送到
transform channel
转换频道
or transform Chandler like we saw before
或像我们之前看到的那样改变钱德勒
is going to receive that message it's
将要收到该消息，这是
going to translate it into a common
要把它翻译成普通的
format which and look at the code here
格式化并在此处查看代码
it's going to think I called it a raw
会以为我叫它是原始的
data don't know what I call it raw data
数据不知道我称之为原始数据
should have been clean data and then
应该是干净的数据，然后
what's going to happen is we saw where
将会发生什么是我们看到了
the transformer is going to send out
变压器要送出去
files and files is actually going to be
文件和文件实际上将是
received up here okay and it's going to
在这里收到了，这将会
write that result out to Bitcoin txt so
将结果写到比特币txt中，以便
now we've created the first half we
现在我们已经创建了上半年
actually created the bottom half of the
实际上创造了
flow we've created the polar and so now
流，我们已经创建了极地，所以现在
we got the coin base let's go ahead and
我们有了硬币的基础，让我们继续前进，
gather that stuff from bitstamp how do
从bitstamp收集这些东西怎么办
we do that so what we're going to do is
我们这样做，所以我们要做的是
go back to my powerpoint coding slide
回到我的PowerPoint编码幻灯片
and there we go and literally I did you
然后我们去了，从字面上我做了你
could what was funny as I said you know
可以像我说的那样有趣吗
that this is not professional job when
那不是专业的工作
you see me recording it then he receipt
你看到我记录下来，然后他回执
backspace backspace backspace backspace
退格键退格键退格键
backspace so in this case it's going to
退格键，因此在这种情况下
be a configuration so just a Java config
是一个配置，所以只是一个Java配置
here and we're going to sound set up an
在这里，我们将进行声音设置
inbound channel adapter it's going to be
入站通道适配器它将是
a we're gonna call it bitstamp HTTP now
一个我们现在将其称为bittamp HTTP
guys I've been when I'd like I said up
我想说的时候我去过的家伙
until you know 40 everything had to be
直到你知道40一切都必须
XML and you saw how much code I had to
XML，您看到了我必须要做的代码
write for that polar ice ax code but the
为那个极地冰斧代码写，但是
XML when I saw this feature come in I
当我看到XML进入此功能时
I've almost cried I can now write a pole
我几乎哭了，现在我可以写一根杆子了
or using annotations it was awesome so
或使用注释都很棒
much so want to give Gary a hug and he
所以非常想给加里一个拥抱，他
joined a track club so he can outrun me
加入了一家田径俱乐部，所以他可以超越我
an art I'm decided to stay in Ukraine no
我决定留在乌克兰的艺术
seriously this is one of those features
认真的，这是这些功能之一
I've been wanting for a long time and
我一直想很久了
finally made it the other thing that we
终于使另一件事，我们
did is basically again it does the same
做的基本上还是一样的
thing it's returning an empty message or
它返回一个空消息或
sending out an empty message once every
每次发送一次空消息
10 seconds and then that is actually
10秒，那实际上是
received by the bitstamp HTTP the
由bitstamp HTTP接收
bitstamp HTTP is going to make a request
bitstamp HTTP将发出一个请求
out to the bitstamp site recruit
到bittamp网站招聘
retrieve the
检索
the JSON with a bit and it's going out
一点点的JSON，它会消失
put that to the transform channel which
放到转换通道上
we already know goes where it goes
我们已经知道去哪里
directly to our files which is going to
直接到我们的文件中
write it out to a file so I think it is
将其写到文件中，所以我认为是
time we show what it looks like so let
时间，我们展示它的样子，所以让
me do that also the read the reason i
我也这样做，读我的原因
recorded this stuff is because our the
记录这些东西是因为我们的
coding there is i made so many mistakes
编码那里我犯了很多错误
when i was trying to practice dude
当我尝试练习花花公子
practice runs i said well i don't record
练习跑，我说不错，我不录音
that like you say here i can't even type
就像你在这里说的，我什至不能打字
it in a knock stuff off the podium so
它从讲台上敲下来的东西，所以
this is the guy that's going to go out
这是要出去的家伙
and gather the data from so this is our
并从中收集数据，这就是我们的
web kept it's going to go out this is
网络保持下去，这将是出去
going to be our web cat wake up a bit
会成为我们的网络猫醒来的
cast or sorry a Bitcoin monitor it's got
投还是对不起一个比特币监视器
a monitor that data and it's going to
监控该数据，它将
crash on me virulent Lee let's see and I
致命的李撞到我身上让我们看看
think I messed up my code there somehow
认为我以某种方式弄乱了我的代码
there we go
我们去
yeah thing I just fixed it will find out
是的，我刚刚修复的东西会发现
very quickly huh
很快啊
and as it's going out gathering that
并且在外出收集时
data let's see if we can there we go and
数据让我们看看是否可以到达目的地
actually have some old code or old stuff
实际上有一些旧代码或旧东西
that was already there but what we can
那已经在那里，但是我们可以
see is now that we're doing the tail
看到现在我们正在做尾巴
once every 10 seconds is going to go out
每10秒要熄灭一次
and gather I mean scroll that up a
并收集我的意思是向上滚动
little bit because I know it's coming up
有点，因为我知道它会来
a little bit love we can see where we're
一点点的爱，我们可以看到我们在哪里
actually getting data from coinbase
实际从coinbase获取数据
current bid is 473 dollars 98 cent for a
当前的价格是473美元98美分
Bitcoin and I can't see the bits Tamplin
比特币，我看不到Tamplin
like from that angle but it's 468 15 we
从那个角度来看，但它是468 15
can actually scroll it up a little bit
实际上可以将其向上滚动一点
here and actually go in and see that the
在这里，实际上进去看看
prices are fluctuating so we're actually
价格在波动，所以我们实际上
getting live data so now you know when
获取实时数据，所以现在您知道何时
you need to buy your bitcoins at what
您需要在什么地方购买比特币
time of day all right so let's go ahead
一天中的好时间，让我们继续吧
and take the next step what is it going
并采取下一步行动
to look like when I have to go in and
看起来像当我必须进去时
actually make it where it can so we're
实际上使它可以做到的，所以我们
going to do bi did I say that wasn't
我会说那不是吗
already nek I lied and we're going to go
我已经撒谎了，我撒谎了，我们要走了
to our transform and from here we're
到我们的转型，从这里开始
going to change it to
将其更改为
right there where we run it and what
就在我们运行它的地方以及什么
we're going to do is while that boots up
我们要做的是在启动时
we're going to actually be writing data
我们实际上将在写数据
out to MQTT by just changing one
只需更改一个即可访问MQTT
transform or sorry the outbound channel
改变或抱歉出站频道
there so while it's doing that's magic
在那里，这是在做魔术
let's go up here you can read my email
让我们上这里你可以阅读我的电子邮件
if you like there we go let me resize
如果您喜欢那里，我们就让我调整大小
that and what we will goes to a review
那，我们将要进行审查
and we can see that we're receiving data
我们可以看到我们正在接收数据
now via the MQTT channel so we're going
现在通过MQTT频道，所以我们要
to show you how a configure a beauty
向您展示如何配置美丽
channel in just a second it's not that
只需一秒钟就可以
much but I wanted to show you just by
很多，但我想向您展示
how if you're testing this stuff you saw
如果您正在测试这些东西，您怎么看
went in and changed one line in this
进去改变了这一行
case it happened to be in in an
万一碰巧在
annotation but you can certainly do this
注解，但您当然可以这样做
directly in XML and that's where I
直接在XML中，这就是我
really like that XML aspect of it where
非常喜欢它的XML方面
I could go in and just say my outbound
我可以进去说出境
channel for my tests are always going to
我的测试渠道总是
go to test output but when I go
去测试输出，但是当我去
production and I have maybe a profile
生产，我可能有个人资料
version of that XML I can have it say
我可以说的那个XML版本
okay it's we're actually going right out
好的，这是我们实际上要马上出发
to the you know the production channel
给你知道生产渠道
so we see we're receiving that good data
所以我们看到我们收到了很好的数据
there so here is my shameless plug for
在那里，这是我无耻的插头
XD Michael forgive me so while as becks
XD Michael宽恕我
t is starting up I want to see XD is
t正在启动，我想看看XD是
basically become as its springs
基本上像它的春天一样
basically actually starting up okay it's
基本上开始就可以了
basically the big one is Springs big
基本上大是斯普林斯大
data initiative to be able to allow you
数据主动性可以让您
to create simple streams for data flow
为数据流创建简单的流
for either translating data getting
用于翻译数据获取
counts pushing data to do executing
计数推送数据以执行
batch jobs so that you can do MapReduce
批处理作业，以便您可以执行MapReduce
stuff but do it in a spring way very
的东西，但非常春季
efficiently but to be able to write
高效但能写
instead of having to write Java code all
不必全部编写Java代码
over the place you can actually do
在你实际可以做的地方
nothing more than just right basic small
只不过是正确的基本小
stream scripts to be able to do that so
流脚本能够做到这一点
how we did it here
我们是怎么做到的
is what we're going to do here is I'm
我们要在这里做的是
going to create a stream food as we see
如我们所见，将创造出流食
here it's going to take in MQTT as they
在这里，他们将采用MQTT
what we call a source this is what's
我们所说的来源是什么
going to be waiting for the sim qtt
将要等待sim qtt
traffic it's going to have a username a
交通将拥有一个用户名
guest pass word is guest remember that
客人密码是客人记住的
when I push data via MQTT it's going to
当我通过MQTT推送数据时，
be pushing it to a topic on our broker
将其推向我们经纪人的主题
so the topic it's going to expect the
因此，该主题将期待
data on is the XD MQTT test and i'm
数据是XD MQTT测试，我
going to just write that data out to a
只是将数据写到
log so let's go ahead and do that now
记录下来，让我们继续并立即执行操作
mind you don't worry about the red I
介意你不用担心红色
actually kicked off the script too early
实际上还为时过早
before XD had a chance to boot up and it
在XD有机会启动之前，它
said hey the bits not there what you're
说，嘿，你那里不存在
talking about so this reason why you saw
谈论所以这就是为什么你看到
that little error but now we can
那个小错误，但是现在我们可以
actually see where spring XD in one line
实际看到spring XD在哪一行
of code yeah yeah as far as you have you
的代码是的，是的，就你所拥有的
could there's all sorts of XD you have
可能有各种各样的XD
the ability to pull in data from HDFS
从HDFS提取数据的能力
file polling tailing files HTTP MQTT JMS
文件轮询尾文件HTTP MQTT JMS
am QR but i'm trying remember also hit
是QR，但我想记住还打了
the spring XD site and you'll see what
春季XD网站，您将看到
we call our sources where we can gather
我们称我们的资源可以聚集
all this data and then write that data
所有这些数据，然后将其写入
out to any number of output and that's
到任何数量的输出，那是
the string that's it and that's what's
就是这样的字符串，那是什么
really cool about it and also i can go
真的很酷，我也可以去
in and now this is running on my local
在现在这正在我的本地上运行
machine if you saw mark Fisher's demo we
机器，如果您看到了马克·费舍尔的演示，我们
had 10 machine or sorry 9 machines
拥有10台计算机，或者遗憾的是有9台计算机
running and all he had to do to handle
跑步和他要做的一切
HTTP file was to write one stream that
HTTP文件是写一个流
says HTTP pipe and then send it off to
说HTTP管道，然后将其发送到
the of the JP pml a processor so you can
JP pml的处理器，因此您可以
go in and sit have a hit have a source
进去坐一下有消息来源
says it's some processor filter
说这是一些处理器过滤器
aggregator counter
聚合计数器
a ton of other things you can tap off of
您可以从中提取很多其他东西
stuff so you can you know get a spawn
东西，所以你可以知道产生一个
feed so that you can send it out to
供稿，以便您可以将其发送到
different streams it's talked to Savi
与Savi交谈的不同流
it's pretty cool but and then have that
这很酷，但是然后
data I'll go out to us a series of
数据，我将向我们提供一系列
sources or sinks yes sir yes you can
源或汇是的，先生，是的，你可以
absolutely one of the things that you're
绝对是你要做的一件事
going to see in a couple of minutes with
几分钟后就会看到
what you get with boot is the ability
启动带来的就是能力
that you can actually have a dot yeah
你实际上可以有一个点呀
mph I'll spring boot when it starts up
mph开机时我会自动开机
does two things when it starts up it
启动时会做两件事
says I'm going to look for any
说我要去找
environment variables out there that are
那里的环境变量是
in the environment so if I'm to pull
在环境中，所以如果我要拉
into a cloud and I have in my cloud to
进入云，我在云中
have certain environment variables have
有某些环境变量
set up it's going to look in the
设置它会在
environment first for property entries
环境优先用于属性输入
right if you can't find the in you're
正确，如果您找不到
asking for a given popular property
要求给定的受欢迎的财产
entry they can't find it out there it's
条目，他们在那里找不到
going to look in your what's called
看看你所谓的
application dot properties or in or
应用程序点属性或
application not you animal they're both
应用不是你，他们都是动物
at that time it's going to then use that
那时它将使用
so I could have set up my application
所以我可以设置我的应用程序
dot properties here put the username
点属性在此处放置用户名
password in there and did it that way so
在那里输入密码，这样
I wouldn't have to enumerate it across
我将不必一一列举
and then it would Eve shrunk it down to
然后它会被夏娃缩小到
stream create name food definition MQTT
流创建名称食物定义MQTT
and then the topics I can even hide the
然后我什至可以隐藏主题
topics if I want to put that in the file
主题，如果我想将其放入文件中
and I can also do that with pretty much
而且我也可以做到这一点
anything that's in there the other thing
里面的任何东西
that you can do is you can write results
你可以做的就是可以写结果
out to Mongo name your favorite was
以蒙哥的名字命名，你最喜欢的是
gonna say name your favorite no sequel
要说出你最喜欢的名字，没有续集
solution write it out to database or was
解决方案将其写出到数据库或
a relational database and all those
关系数据库以及所有这些
entries for configuring all that
配置所有条目
actually show up in your llamo file or I
实际出现在您的llamo文件中还是我
say gamma but also your properties file
说伽玛，但你的属性文件
it's interchangeable sire likes ya mo so
可以互换的父亲喜欢亚莫
you always see as demos using ammo but
你总是看到使用弹药的演示，但是
it also supports properties so like I
它也支持属性，就像我
said one line you're pretty much done
说一句话，你差不多完成了
like we actually could go out and have a
就像我们实际上可以出去并有一个
beer right now but i'm going to show you
啤酒现在，但我将向您展示
the spring boot stuff because it's still
spring boot 的东西，因为它仍然
cool any other questions on next D
在下一个D上冷却其他问题
before I move on yes sir go right ahead
在我继续前进之前，先生，请继续
I would say that the thing that
我会说那件事
separates us up Oh ESB and XD how they
分开我们哦ESB和XD他们如何
fit in that space in this way where you
以这种方式适合您的空间
can schedule I'm going to probably let
可以安排我可能要让
that savvy answer that because he does
那个聪明的答案，因为他确实
more of affairs of contrast but my
更多的对比事务，但我的
knowledge of es DS and this is you you
ES DS的知识，这就是你
can schedule batch jobs it's very easy
可以安排批处理作业，这非常容易
to be able to distribute that data out
以便将数据分发出去
across multiple nodes try to think of
跨多个节点尝试思考
some other things here but yeah
这里还有其他一些东西，是的
but batch but also live feed like we're
但批处理，但也像我们
seeing here this MQTT stuff so it's
在这里看到这个MQTT的东西，所以
really meant to handle large amounts of
真的意味着要处理大量
data we're like typically SBS they kind
我们通常喜欢的SBS数据
of choked out after a certain point this
在某一点之后被this住了
allows you to be able to handle large
使您能够处理大型
amounts of data as it as it may be
可能的数据量
coming in you also can specify large
进来也可以指定大
files process those files push them to
文件处理那些文件将它们推送到
HDFS be able to read files off HDFS and
HDFS能够读取HDFS和
you can schedule batch jobs you can also
您可以安排批处理作业，也可以
kick off batch jobs based on events it's
根据事件启动批处理作业
a really rich set of features it can be
可以提供非常丰富的功能
but I'm not sure that it's the deer
但我不确定那是鹿
sense where spring integration is really
感觉春天整合真正在哪里
more its fits inside of a Java app right
更适合Java应用程序
I have a Java app that which I need to
我有一个Java应用程序，我需要
be able to handle the the you know
能够处理你所知道的
there's a certain pattern that we have
我们有某种模式
that matches or pattern patterns that
匹配或图案化
are part of that eip or Enterprise
是该eip或Enterprise的一部分
enterprise integration patterns that
企业整合模式
this fits and Saul's that's where in a
这很适合，而扫罗在那
you know you're going to be able to use
你知道你将能够使用
spring integration but if I've got to be
Spring Integration ，但如果我必须
able to give the ability to you know
能够赋予你所知的能力
higher level users the ability to go in
高级用户进入的能力
and write you know scripts be able to
并写出您知道的脚本能够
process flow and make it distributed
处理流程并使之分布
across and to handle large amounts I can
跨越并处理大量我可以
certainly do that using this also with
当然也可以使用
XD there was discussion by David
XD进行了David的讨论
turetsky and Patrick and Peralta on
turetsky和Patrick和Peralta
Wednesday forgive me know it's Tuesday
星期三原谅我知道现在是星期二
it's Tuesday where they actually cover
实际上是星期二
how to build the components or the what
如何构建组件或什么
we call our adapters that are not our
我们称我们的适配器不是我们的
module called modules modules that are
称为模块的模块
not already there so if you have a
还没有在那里，所以如果你有一个
specific module that you need maybe
您可能需要的特定模块
something we don't do out of the box you
我们没有开箱即用的东西
can write your own and there's actually
可以写自己的，实际上有
XD site shows you how to do that which
XD网站向您展示了如何做到这一点
is pretty cool and if you liked it a lot
非常酷，如果您非常喜欢
send it to us and when you get a free
发送给我们，当您获得免费
t-shirt from us but actually
来自我们的T恤，但实际上
contributing back this is all by the way
一路回馈
XD is all open source so pull it down
XD都是开源的，因此请下拉
play with it you even have XD ec2 out
玩它，您甚至可以获得XD ec2
there
那里
where if you're an ec2 user it will
如果您是ec2用户，它将在哪里
deploy XD to up to how many containers
部署XD最多可容纳多少个容器
and all you have to do is fill in a
而您要做的就是填写一个
properties file and it will actually go
属性文件，它实际上会
out there and do that for you so one
在那里为你做到这一点
stop shop for big data processing and
停站进行大数据处理
handling and report running and batch
处理并报告运行和批处理
jobs and windows doors and vacuums all
工作和窗户门和吸尘器全部
right any other questions on next d cool
对下一个酷的任何其他问题
all right savvy now owes me $25 I'll pay
现在精通我欠我$ 25
that to my daughter for all the times I
一直给我女儿
said XD instant integration all right so
说XD即时整合还可以
we're going to kill XD here and unlike
我们要在这里杀死XD，不像
in marks discussion I only had one node
在标记讨论中，我只有一个节点
so I just killed it right there so it
所以我就在那里杀了它
killed that right there so this guy's
在那里杀了那个人，所以这个家伙的
still emitting away right the monitor so
仍然会向显示器右侧发射
he's still cranking he's sending stuff
他仍然在发动东西
out and so let's go ahead and take a
出去，所以让我们继续
quick break yet it says hey I try to
快速休息，但它说嘿，我尝试
write somebody night bye guys gone now
写某人晚上再见家伙现在走了
what happened so we're going to spend
发生了什么事，所以我们要花钱
just a second here on MPT okay and I'm
在MPT上只需要一秒钟，我就
going to cover the adapter as it as it
照原样覆盖适配器
stands in the 40 and then we're going to
站在40，然后我们将
cover some stuff that comes in the 41
涵盖41中的一些东西
release so with the 40 with the MQTT is
发布，因此带有MQTT的40是
looks like the following we're using the
如下所示，我们正在使用
PAHO as a factory and I'm sorry about
泛美卫生组织作为工厂，对此我感到抱歉
this you know what I can do I can slide
这你知道我能做什么我可以滑
this away there we go and slide that
这走到那里，我们去滑动
back over here so our client factory is
回到这里，所以我们的客户工厂是
for coming from that the default you're
来自默认的
using the Pahoa client factory it
使用Pahoa客户端工厂
requires a username password for
需要输入用户名密码
authentication into rabbit it's again
认证进入兔子再次
it's receiving data on the MQTT out
它在MQTT上接收数据
channel its ideas MQTT outbound the
引导其思想MQTT出站
client ID every MQTT requires a unique
每个MQTT的客户ID都需要唯一
client ID it's not really enforced by
客户ID并没有真正实施
the broker but it's a way where you you
经纪人，但这是您的一种方式
know we did say
知道我们确实说过
authenticating using the gasp that's
使用的喘气进行身份验证
just the kind of the login to indicate
只是指示登录的种类
the device that you sit that you're
您所坐的设备
actually receiving the data from has to
实际接收到的数据必须
have a client ID and it's supposed to be
有一个客户ID，应该是
supposed to be unique in your network
应该在您的网络中是唯一的
but in this case I just chose guest so
但在这种情况下，我只是选择了客人
again this is just to uh sound fun the
再次，这只是听起来很有趣
URL is with a broker that we're going to
URL与我们要转到的代理一起
be emitting our data to this is again
再次发出我们的数据
our outbound channel this is for Bitcoin
我们的出站通道，这是针对比特币的
monitor the default topic I want to
监视我想要的默认主题
write to is the XDM qtd test then we
写到是XDM qtd测试，然后我们
have what's called our default quality
有所谓的默认质量
of service or quality of service stands
服务或服务台的质量
for your get loud by the spec you're
让您按规格大声说话
allowed three and i cannot remember the
允许三个，我不记得了
exact names but they're as follows zero
确切名称，但它们如下零
says look it's a sinned and forget type
说看，这是一种犯罪和忘记的类型
of thing i'm going to send it if it
我要发送的东西
makes it to the M qt or makes it to the
达到M qt或达到
broker great if it doesn't make it to
经纪人很棒，如果它不能做到
the broker message is gone you can have
经纪人消息不见了，你可以拥有
qos a one that stipulates that I'm going
qos一个规定我要去的人
to keep sending this message until it
继续发送此消息直到它
finally receives it so you can actually
最终收到它，这样您就可以
get duplicates ins and then you have to
获取重复的ins，然后您必须
which stands for hey I'm receiving I've
代表嘿，我收到了
only send it only once it's more
只发送一次
intensive processor wise but a
明智的密集处理器
guarantees that message only be sent
保证仅发送消息
once default retained stands for when
默认保留一次代表何时
the queue is basically says it's an
队列基本上是说
instruction to the server it says look
服务器说它看起来的指令
if you've received this message and it
如果您已收到此消息及其
has a default retain set to true it says
它说默认保留设置为true
I want you to hold that message because
我希望您保留该消息，因为
it might be a long time before the next
下一次可能要很长时间
time you receive this message so you
您收到此消息的时间，因此您
need to act as if this message is going
需要表现得好像这条消息要走
to be here for a while so and it says
在这里待了一会儿，它说
the next time you receive a message
下次您收到消息时
replace it with a new message but it
用新消息替换它，但是它
means to retain it if you said it
如果您说的话意味着保留它
defaults it says look you can do
默认它说你可以做的样子
whatever you want to the message drop it
不管您想给它留言什么
once you're done with it so that's kind
一旦完成它，那就好了
of what that is but let's go ahead and
那是什么，但让我们继续前进，
look at what we're doing in the 41 let's
看看我们在41中所做的
go ahead and go there I think I may have
去吧，去那里，我想我可能有
jumped a slide or two
跳了一两张幻灯片
and there we go i don't think i did
然后我们走了，我不认为我做到了
alright so the latest in 241 so is EXO
好吧，所以241的最新消息是EXO
spring integration oh my oh my dollar
Spring Integration 哦，我的天，我的美元
daughter Darwin said spring XD there
女儿达尔文说那里有春天XD
again spring integration for one is
再一次 Spring Integration 是
actually taking advantage of one of the
实际上利用其中之一
requests that we got from the community
我们从社区得到的要求
was the ability for high ability high
高能力高
availability and some performance
可用性和一些性能
requests we are now doing a sink sins
要求我们现在正在犯下沉罪
right now it's a blocking sin so if you
现在这是一种阻碍性的罪恶，所以如果你
go to full one you can actually do an
全力以赴，你实际上可以做一个
asynchronous into your MQTT high
异步进入您的MQTT高
availability and so now where you saw
可用性，所以现在您看到的地方
before in our example we had URL you can
在我们的示例中，我们之前有可以使用的URL
scratch that URL and have put in server
抓取该URL并放入服务器
URI so you can actually a new numerate
URI，因此您实际上可以使用新的数字
multiple you are brokers that you may
您可能是多个经纪人
send to in case of a broker failure you
如果经纪人失败，请发送至
can send it over you now can set your
可以发送给您现在可以设置您的
quality of service for each subscription
每个订阅的服务质量
and also you can go in and set up our
而且您也可以进入并设置我们的
subscriber unsubscribe from topix at
订户从以下位置取消订阅topix
runtime one of the other questions I get
运行时我遇到的其他问题之一
about MQTT what are what does a spec say
关于MQTT规范怎么说
about security how can i prevent
关于安全我该如何预防
somebody you know pushing bad topics in
您认识的某人在推销坏话题
in this KR bad messages to a topic NQ TT
在此KR中向主题NQ TT发送的错误消息
does support in the standard as of the
自该标准开始支持
31 standard user name and password as we
和我们一样31个标准的用户名和密码
just saw it does not have anything on
刚刚看到它没有任何东西
encryption but people are commonly using
加密，但人们通常在使用
ssl but ssl can be heavy so that's just
ssl但ssl可能很重，所以
a kind of one design decisions you have
您拥有的一种设计决策
to make you can have your application
使您可以拥有您的应用程序
encrypt portions of it or dcrit or what
加密其中的一部分或décrit或其他内容
will say redact certain portions of the
会说删除部分内容
message that are sensitive you can
您可以敏感的邮件
certainly do that authorization while
当然在做那个授权
rabbit does not allow or specify that a
兔子不允许或指定
client can write to a given topic there
客户可以在那里写给定主题
are brokers that do support that so I
是经纪人支持的，所以我
can't say those because i work for
不能说那些，因为我为
pivotal
关键的
pivotal has rabbit but there are guys
关键有兔子，但有家伙
that actually around for authorization
实际上是为了授权
so if the client does request a right to
因此，如果客户确实要求获得
a specific topic you can actually have
您实际上可以拥有的特定主题
it where it can specify offer I swear
它可以指定我发誓的地方
they can writer or not world peace is
他们可以写或不写世界和平是
not on that speck but it is planned for
不在那个斑点上，但计划用于
boot 20 when it's out there so world
当它在那里时引导20
peace will be handled by boob 20 sorry
和平将由布布20抱歉
that just fell flat on the floor and I
刚倒在地板上，我
apologize oh so finishing up the let's
抱歉，让我们结束吧
go ahead and start our MQTT I'm gonna
继续并开始我们的MQTT
try to get you all out here early
尽早把大家带到这里
because I know y'all are tired and you
因为我知道你们都累了
know I've had fun but sir go ahead
知道我玩得开心，但是先生
message sighs and it huh oh yes he says
消息叹了口气，是的，他说
why would I use MQTT which what would be
为什么我要使用MQTT
decided deciding the criteria between
决定决定之间的标准
MQTT or amq that's a fantastic question
MQTT或amq这是一个很棒的问题
it really comes down to mq is richer ok
真正归结为mq更丰富
it's larger but MQTT is meant to be
它更大，但是MQTT的目的是
small and it's specifically for devices
很小，专门用于设备
because we're again goes back to the
因为我们再次回到
original discussion it was creative for
最初的讨论很有创意
devices where battery or bandwidth is
电池或带宽为
critical so it's you you can look at say
至关重要，所以你可以看看
you know what in this case may be we
你知道在这种情况下我们
want to reduce network traffic maybe we
想减少网络流量，也许我们
want to have it where you know where
想要把它放在你知道的地方
it's all internal we really don't really
都是内部的，我们真的不是真的
need to worry about securing this
需要担心确保这一点
message because of the low priority
消息，因为优先级低
certainly can do that so that's that
当然可以做到这一点
would be to me the deciding factor
对我来说是决定性因素
certainly again there's multiple brokers
当然又有多个经纪人
that support both activemq hive rabbit
同时支持activemq蜂巢兔
support it so it's on most of the major
支持它，所以它在大多数主要
vendors so for i'll try to pick it up
供应商，所以我会尝试捡起来
and i know i kind of dawdled a little
我知道我有点kind
bit here so setting up but we're going
在这里，所以设置，但我们要去
to do for MQTT listener is i'm going to
我要做的是MQTT监听器
show you the build-up Gradle it is
告诉你它是什么
so sexy you're going to love it because
如此性感，你会爱上它，因为
it's small I like small griddle files
很小，我喜欢小的扒手文件
the other is we're going to talk we're
另一个是我们要谈的是
going to not really set up for
不会真正为
integration XML but I want it again for
集成XML，但我再次想要
the guys are using XML and love it boots
伙计们正在使用XML并喜欢它的启动
there for you it still supports it and
在那里，它仍然支持它，并且
it will always support it because
它会一直支持它，因为
Springs not getting rid of that at all
斯普林斯一点都没有摆脱
so you're in good shape there and we're
所以你那里的状态很好，我们
going to show you how to set up the main
将向您展示如何设置主
so we're going to do now let's take a
所以我们现在要做的是
look at our bill Gradle file this is
看看我们的Bill Gradle文件，这是
just an excerpt in this case what we're
在这种情况下只是摘录
going to be looking at is to have boot
要看的是要启动
in your XML file or so you're if you're
在您的XML文件中，或者如果您在
using maven pom we just happen to using
使用maven pom，我们碰巧使用
build.gradle but let you know Dave siren
build.gradle，但让您知道戴夫警报器
loves Navin he does not like Gradle so
爱纳文，他不喜欢Gradle，所以
maven is what he'll write everybody else
他将写给其他人的专家
has go behind and write Gradle for him
已经落后并为他写了Gradle
but so you're supported both ways
但是，这两种方式都支持您
because we spring support certainly both
因为我们肯定支持
and I like both because again it depends
我都喜欢，因为这又取决于
on the need but in this case all you
根据需要，但在这种情况下，
have to do is apply a plug-in of spring
要做的是应用弹簧插件
boot above that you can see where we
在上面启动，您可以看到我们在哪里
have added a dependency in our build
在我们的构建中添加了依赖项
script repository so once you've applied
脚本存储库，因此一旦应用
that plug-in you're allowed to use what
该插件，您可以使用
we call starter palms and basically this
我们称之为初学者手掌，基本上这是
goes back to the convention side right
回到约定的右边
so we said Mark Fisher I think maybe
所以我们说Mark Fisher我想
even gary was on that worked with Dave
甚至gary都在与Dave合作
and they said okay what do we need to
他们说好，我们需要什么
put in spring integration so they
进行 Spring Integration ，因此他们
created a spring integration starter
创建了一个Spring Integration Starter
palm so say you haven't added you know
手掌，所以说你还没有添加，你知道
three or four dependencies or whatever
三个或四个依赖项
just needed the starter palm it's ready
只需要入门手掌就可以了
to rock but notice two lines below that
晃动，但请注意下面的两行
you see where we have the MQTT plugin
您会看到我们有MQTT插件
why is that because commonly people do
为什么会这样，因为通常人们会这样做
not use MQTT in their daily lives it's
不要在日常生活中使用MQTT
more EMQ right so that would be there
更多的EMQ对，以便在那里
but MQTT isn't but that doesn't mean
但这不是MQTT，但这并不意味着
we're out of the war you know out of
我们已经摆脱了战争
luck it just means that we just need to
运气就意味着我们只需要
add that to it okay so those ones a
加上它好吧，那些那些
little side you get it is convention
你得到的一面是惯例
that you will be using am cute as
你会很可爱
convention that you'll be using file
约定您将使用文件
adapters they'll be convinced
适配器，他们将被说服
to use this feature of that feature MQTT
使用该功能的MQTT的此功能
is certainly well you needed but it's
当然是您需要的，但这是
not always required so again it's an
并不总是必需的，所以这又是一个
opinion I'd sure thing came chose
认为我确定事情来了
wrongly because I like MQTT but that's
错误地因为我喜欢MQTT但那是
our thing so we're going to go back to
我们的事情，所以我们要回去
our magic coder real quick and we're
我们的魔术编码器真的很快，我们
going to go ahead and set up our spring
继续前进，设置我们的春天
boot app and short we're going to make a
启动应用程序，简短的说，我们将制作一个
controller so yes this is going to
控制器，是的，这将
actually have a UI component to it and
实际上有一个UI组件
you'll see my brilliant beautiful skills
你会看到我灿烂的美丽技能
at writing you I the only things you
在给你写信时，我只有你
didn't see on this slide is I actually
在这张幻灯片上没看到的是我实际上
do have the web starter so that's reason
确实有网络启动器，这就是原因
why we're allowed to to do that also
为什么我们也被允许这样做
you'll see that we are we used enable
您会看到我们使用了enable
auto configuration so at least by the
自动配置，至少
end of this this conference you should
在本次会议结束时，您应该
have seen enable auto configuration like
已经看到启用自动配置
18 times because it's that's you know
18次，因为那是你知道的
basically that says hey spring boot
基本上说嘿靴子
based on the starter palms based on
基于入门手掌
convention let's configure my app this
约定让我们配置我的应用
way so that's what it's using what I'm
这样，那就是它正在使用我的
not afraid to put right underneath that
不怕放在下面
is import resource for our integration
是我们整合的进口资源
XML that we're using we're doing nothing
我们正在使用的XML无所作为
down here but setting up our request
在这里，但建立我们的要求
mapping response body actually I got
实际上我得到了映射响应体
tagged by Josh saying oh you can do that
由乔什（Josh）标记说，哦，你可以做到的
one line now know it okay so I was
一条线现在知道了，所以我
ashamed and then finally we're setting
ham愧，最后我们开始
up our service activator so our service
激活我们的服务激活器，以便我们提供服务
activator is going in and it's going to
激活剂将要进入
be receiving data from output and will
正在从输出接收数据，并将
show you where that's coming from any
告诉你这是哪里来的
from the xml and all it's doing is it's
从xml中开始，它所做的就是
going to print the value it receives to
将打印接收到的值
console and then it's going to up our
控制台，然后我们的
counter by one so it says okay we
一口气反驳说好吧我们
received a message okay so what did that
收到消息好，那是什么
do for us this is getting it's my chance
为我们做这是我的机会
every time a drop down my voice gets
每当我的声音下降时
bassy so let's go to hear start off I up
低音，让我们开始聆听我的声音
and you can already see where we ran it
您已经可以看到我们在哪里运行了
before but
但是之前
and what we can do now so in this case
在这种情况下，我们现在可以做些什么
all we're doing is basically what XD did
我们要做的基本上就是XD所做的
for us before where it goes out and it's
对我们来说，在它消失之前
going to be hooking up to a client for
将与客户联系
the MQTT right and listening to that
MQTT权利并听取
topic so what does that look like and
主题，那看起来像什么，
when we talked about the XML again again
当我们再次谈论XML时
it's the client factory and remember
这是客户工厂，请记住
that our service activator was looking
我们的服务激活者正在寻找
for output and we gave it a really
为输出，我们给了它一个真正的
auspicious weird client ID like we
像我们这样的吉祥怪异客户ID
talked about before even on this is a
甚至在这之前谈论过
device that's listening it has to have a
正在监听的设备必须有一个
unique ID again it's not really enforced
唯一的ID并没有真正执行
but you know let's play along again the
但是你知道我们一起玩
URL is to localhost but again if you're
URL是本地主机，但如果您是
using you can use service you are is so
使用您可以使用的服务是如此
you can support more than one broker you
您可以支持多个经纪人
can receive more than one topic you can
可以收到一个以上的主题
be monitoring more than one topic in
监视多个主题
this case where the ganges only one
在这种情况下，恒河只有一个
really monitoring next EDS XD MQTT test
真正监视下一个EDS XD MQTT测试
send timeout says basically if the if
发送超时基本上说如果
I'm writing to a channel that could be
我正在写一个可能是
blocked I can set up a time out for that
阻止，我可以为此设置超时
and that's it and now what we should be
就是这样，现在我们应该是
seeing here is this sir
看到这是这位先生
is what you just showed and it tells you
是你刚刚展示的，它告诉你
there is that now you've now replaced
现在您已经更换了
that with some code you're basically
有了一些代码，你基本上
doing the same thing what's that as far
做同样的事情，到目前为止
as they get the message it just right
当他们得到正确的信息时
yeah in this case what this is this is
是的，在这种情况下，这是什么
actually a spring boot app doing it
实际上是一个 spring boot 应用程序
where before let's let me I can bring up
在哪之前让我让我长大
the IntelliJ here we can look at the
IntelliJ在这里我们可以看一下
main oh yeah that yes exactly yeah yeah
主要哦，是的，是的，是的，是的
in the stream before is I just ran XD
在我刚刚运行XD之前
and then deploy the stream to it and it
然后将流部署到它
was monitoring it I shut down XD because
正在监视它，我关闭了XD，因为
if not they'll be fighting for the topic
如果没有，他们会为这个话题而战
well actually wouldn't be fighting
其实不会打架
actually both getting a entry off the
实际上都是从
topic but just wanted to go ahead and
主题，但只是想继续前进，
show yeah XD can do it in one line vote
显示是的，XD可以在一线表决中做到
did it a couple more but boot is
多做几下，但是启动是
probably what we're going to be writing
可能是我们要写的
our code in so what did we get for free
我们的代码，所以我们免费获得了什么
so the one thing I want to also show you
所以我也想告诉你一件事
here is if we go back to look at our
这是我们回头看看
Gradle file remember I said I in that
Gradle文件记得我在那说过
last little cut I left out the starter
最后一点削减我省掉了首发
palm for web but also you're going to
掌上网络，但你也要
see something we call an hour actuator
看到我们称之为小时执行器的东西
and we're going to show you what the
我们将向您展示
actuator does for us we're free okay
执行器为我们做的我们有空吗
again what spring boot does is it says
spring boot 又说了什么
if you as you add the starter palms it's
如果您添加初学者手掌，
going to change the default behavior or
将要更改默认行为或
the that you get with your application
您从应用程序中获得的
so the starter web gave me free MVC so
所以入门网站给了我免费的MVC，所以
what did that mean so if I can go take a
这是什么意思，所以如果我可以去
look at what that would go for as I do
看看我会做什么
localhost 8080 and now it says the count
本地主机8080，现在它说计数
is production dash dash 36 and I'll talk
是生产破折号36，我会说
about what that you know the question
关于你所知道的问题
you may ask is like where did that come
你可能会问那是从哪里来的
from especially when you're let me go
特别是当你放开我
back to the real thing here where did
回到真实的东西在这里做了
that come from remember how we talked
来自于我们如何交谈
about before that spring boot when it
大约在那个 spring boot 之前
starts up looks at the environment
开始看环境
variables and it says I'm gonna look for
变量，它说我要寻找
display message I can't find environment
显示消息我找不到环境
variables do you have a application type
变量，您是否有应用程序类型
properties file out there answer is yes
属性文件在那里答案是
I did
我做了
you but more importantly if I kind of
你，但更重要的是，如果我有点
scroll this over not all that actually
滚动而不是全部
I've noted it too there we go you see I
我也注意到了，我们去吧，你看到我
have an application debt production dot
有申请债务产生点
properties file and it says the count is
属性文件，它说计数是
production dot dot but you said I
生产点点，但你说我
thought you said is application type
以为你说的是​​应用程序类型
properties also for free it also sets up
属性也是免费的，它也设置
java or sorry spring profiles so if i go
Java或抱歉的春季概况，所以如果我去
in there and i set in my particular run
在那儿，我开始我的特定跑步
environment if we go out here and take a
环境，如果我们出去这里，
look at it and I go in and I say set
看着它，我进去，说集
pipe grep spring I set my profiles to
我将我的配置文件设置为
production so I can actually have
生产，所以我实际上可以
different application dot properties
不同的应用点属性
right oh well ha there we go we're going
好的，哦，哈哈，我们要走了
we yep yeah we can see where we have
是的，我们可以看到我们在哪里
spring profiles active equals production
弹簧轮廓有效等于产量
so what it does is that in spring XD it
所以它的作用是在春季XD中
says okay if I'm going to default look
说可以，如果我要使用默认外观
for always application dot properties
始终适用于点属性
but I can go in and set up my
但我可以进去设置我的
environment available of spring active
春季活动的可用环境
profiles or so our spring profiles
型材或我们的弹簧型材
active and based on that it's going to
活跃，并基于此
say ok I set a production it's going to
说好吧，我要设定一个生产
look for applications dash production
寻找应用冲刺生产
dot properties and it's going to use
点属性，它将被使用
that but if I wanted to say unset spring
那但是如果我想说春天
profiles active and we do the pset you
配置文件处于活动状态，我们会为您设置pset
don't see anything there and i restart
没有看到任何东西，我重新启动
my environment sorry about that let it
我的环境对此感到抱歉
get started I get see this magic spring
开始吧，我来看看这个神奇的春天
oh by the way you can also change the
哦，顺便说一句，您也可以更改
application top properties to something
应用程序顶级属性
else you want if you look at spring XD
否则，如果您查看Spring XD，
you can actually go in and you'll see
你实际上可以走进去，你会看到
where its next detail properties right
下一个详细信息属性正确的位置
but yeah you had a question
但是是的，你有一个问题
I can shrink it this one like that often
我可以经常这样缩小它
okay I like that there we go but now if
好吧，我喜欢我们走了，但是现在，如果
i go back to my browser and i hit
我回到浏览器，然后点击
refresh there you go so by just changing
刷新你去那里，所以只需更改
the spring profile is active i have the
春天的轮廓是活跃的，我有
ability to change whether i'm running in
更改我是否正在跑步的能力
QA development or production which is
进行质量检查开发或生产
and how much code did I write for that
我为此写了多少代码
that's free but what if I want to
那是免费的，但是如果我想
measure this the health of my system
衡量我系统的健康状况
which is very critical especially when
这是非常关键的，尤其是当
you're talking about spring XD that's
您正在谈论的是Spring XD
got you know 10 containers that are
知道了10个容器
handling having to handle a lot of data
处理必须处理大量数据
so let's go to our ye old fashioned
所以我们去老式的
jconsole and one of the things you get
jconsole和你得到的东西之一
for free once you turn on actuator is
在您打开执行器后免费
this Bitcoin MTT yes sir we're going to
这个比特币MTT是的，先生，我们要
connect don't tell my mom i go on secure
连接不要告诉我妈妈我继续安全
connections hit em beans now i could
现在我可以连接到em豆了
actually go in and look at endpoints and
实际上去看看端点
look at a thread dump of my app i can
看看我的应用程序的线程转储
actually go in and get metrics and let
实际上进入并获取指标，然后
us see what kind of machine my
我们看看我的机器是什么
application is deployed to mem free
应用程序部署到免费内存
memory processors etc i even have a
内存处理器等，我什至有一个
health endpoint status up basically
健康端点状态基本上升
that's the faulted for spring boot it
这是 spring boot 的缺点
always says up but what if i want to
总是说，但是如果我想
have something that's more meaningful to
有一些更有意义的东西
me as my app how do I know my
我作为我的应用程序我怎么知道我的
application is up and running how can I
应用程序已启动并正在运行
set that up I can actually go back to my
设置好我实际上可以回到我的
main let's go ahead and terminate that
主要让我们继续并终止该操作
yet again poor guys probably wondering
可怜的人又想知道
why I keep turning it on them off let's
为什么我一直将其关闭
go back to hear we're going back to our
回去听听我们要回到我们的
main I say I wasn't going to go to any
主要我说我不会去任何
coding I'm going to do just a little bit
编码我只要做一点
we're going to implement health
我们要实施健康
ok
好
and are actually is indicator oh sorry
其实是指标哦对不起
no wonder it didn't work
难怪它没有用
there we go and we're going to have it
我们去了，我们将要拥有它
helped me out a little bit here want to
帮我一点点在这里想
implement the methods and it gives us a
实施方法，它给我们一个
health method that we have to fulfill so
我们必须满足的健康方法
how we do that we say health health
我们怎么说，我们说健康
equals health dot and you notice that we
等于健康点，您会注意到我们
have some defaults here we have I can
这里有一些默认值，我们可以
set my own status I can say down up
设定我自己的身份我可以说不定
unknown but in this case I'm gonna give
未知，但在这种情况下，我要给
it my own special status so we're going
这是我自己的特殊身份，所以我们要
to go ahead and give the status of
继续前进，并给予地位
everything is ok but let's say if the
一切都还好，但是如果
counter is equal to 0 we want to say
计数器等于0我们想说
health equals health dot status not okay
健康等于健康网点状态不好
and I'd forgot to do this build and go
我忘了做这个建造
up here and do that as well
在这里也做
now what we should see is if our counter
现在我们应该看到的是我们的柜台
0 what we should see is I'm not healthy
0我们应该看到的是我不健康
and if it's healthy it should say I'm or
如果身体健康，应该说我或
if I'm not see if i gotta count greater
如果我不知道我是否要数更多
than zero should see okay but the other
比零应该可以，但是另一个
is if I not if I have a counter of 0 I
如果我没有，如果我的计数器为0
should say not okay huh what'd I miss oh
应该说不好吧呵呵我想念哦
thank you well return null calls us to
谢谢您，请返回null致电我们
crash quite efficiently actually it just
实际上非常有效地崩溃
throws an exception so there we go and
引发异常，所以我们去了
let's go to the other thing that you get
让我们去看看你得到的另一件事
through actuator that you can it comes
通过执行器就可以实现
out by default is localhost you can
默认情况下是localhost
actually go into hit and the health
实际上受到打击和健康
right out the gate in this case it's not
就在这种情况下，不是
going to yeah i think i just got spammed
是的，我想我刚收到垃圾邮件
there we go everything is ok because
我们去那里一切都很好，因为
it's actually picked up messages i was
实际上是我收到的邮件
hoping a let's see if I can catch up
希望让我们看看我能不能赶上
again and try that one more time let's
再试一次，让我们
see if I can get it to cradle run
看看我是否可以摇篮
okay there we go let's try now
好吧，我们去吧，现在尝试
not okay so what we're seeing now is I
不好，所以我们现在看到的是我
didn't have any messages process so it's
没有任何消息处理，所以
saying hey so now we can actually go in
说嘿，所以现在我们可以实际进入
and check through HTTP or go over here
并通过HTTP进行检查或在此处进行检查
again back to our we lost our connection
再次回到我们，我们失去了联系
that's okay we're closing up real quick
没关系，我们很快就会关闭
here echoing listener connect secure
在这里呼应监听器连接安全
mbeans framework and point health
mbeans框架和健康点
attributes data and there we go
属性数据，然后我们去
everything is ok but you can actually go
一切都很好，但是你实际上可以去
in from your here and do metrics like we
从您这里来，并执行类似我们的指标
showed before can actually go in and see
之前显示的可以实际进入并看到
what beans are deployed and you know
部署了哪些bean，您知道
that's it so just go back to our
就是这样，只要回到我们的
presentation of happiness and the magic
展现幸福与魔力
happens here now there we go we can see
发生在这里，现在去，我们可以看到
that's it so now you actually have
就是这样，现在您实际上已经拥有
create be able to create a spring boot
创建能够创建 spring boot
app which you can actually go in and
您可以实际进入的应用程序
have data flows in it using integration
使用集成将数据流放入其中
I can check the health status of it and
我可以检查它的健康状况并
all I have to do is add a couple of
我要做的就是加几个
actuator or add a couple starter pumps
执行器或添加几个起动泵
and you're ready to rock all right guys
你已经准备好摇滚所有的家伙
any questions alright guys thank you
任何问题，好的，谢谢
you
您